

Kristina Klepik

Front-End Developer

kristina.klepik.by@gmail.com

+375291471486

-1-----

Gomel, Belarus

linkedin.com/in/kristina-klepik in

github.com/Kristy-user

I started to learn web development last year. It was an informed choice to change my profession, so I'm very motivated to develop my career. I've become interested in Frontend development because I can immediately see the result of my work. Also there are many ways to create a product and you can always do better. Now I'm practicing Frontend with Codecademy and taking English lessons. As for interests, in my free time I enjoy sports.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graduate TeachMeSkills

08/2021 - 04/2022

Belarus, Minsk

The studing consisted of 208 academic hours, during which I studied: • fundamenta HTML, CSS; • Git and GitHub; • JavaScript Syntax; • TypeScript; • API, Web storage API; • Async JS and HTTP Requests; • React (HOC, Router, Context, Hooks); • Redux (middleware, Reduxthunk | Redux-saga);

Достижения:

- Graduate work web-application MyFitnessApp. This app allows to manage your sport activities and it helps people to reach and control their sports goals. In the course of this development, I set up Webpack by myself, used functional components with their hooks, learned and practiced ReactJS, Redux, Node.JS, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ajax, API, REST.
- GitHub repo: https://github.com/Kristyuser/MyFitnessApp
- All projects your can find here: github.com/Kristy-user

Visa officer VFS BY LLC

02/2019 - 08/2021

Belarus, Gomel

During this work, were improved such skills as communication, attentiveness, quickness.

Priorbank JSC Banking OfficerPriorbank JSC

02/2013 - 10/2018

Belarus, Gomel

During this work, were improved such skills as communication, emotional stability, scrupulousness to digital data, analytical thinking.

EDUCATION

Front-End Developer

TeachMeSkills

08/2021 - 04/2022

Belarus, Minsk

Manager-economist

Sukhoi State Technical University of Gomel

09/2009 - 06/2013

Belarus, Gomel

SKILLS

HTML, CSS / SCSS, JavaScript, OOP, ReactJS, Redux, Node.js, Ajax, API, REST, Git

CERTIFICATES

Front - End Developer (08/2021 - 04/2022)

TeachMeSkills LLC (Minsk, Belarus

Learn TypeScript (05/2022)

Codeacademy

Create a Front-End App with React Skill Path (04/2022)

Codecademy

Learn JavaScript Course (04/2022)

Codecademy

LANGUAGES

English: B1